[Music]
so there are many metropic that are
working with limitate the acetylcholine
pathway for instance they're working
parts of the assumed : pathway say we're
looking at choline donors some choline
donors are going to affect peripheral
neurons more or going to affect central
nervous and more and they didn't have
different plasma times and what is the
right kind of balance between the
choline donors the acetyl donors the
NMDA modulators but because it's
necessary the acetylcholine esterase
does a whole bunch of parts such as any
particular pathway that has to be
thought of in a fairly nuanced way to
make sure that there's no rate limiting
functions that aren't being addressed
and then that's just one pathway so
again there are many snacks that will
work on the table correlate or that'll
work on dopamine or catecholamines more
widely or glutamate all of those are
part of what we're wanting to affect
right in any of the beta access support
mitochondrial biogenesis and the ETP
support larger structural effects like
synaptogenesis and neurogenesis were
actually having connectomics changes so
I would say that the big things that are
unique about our formulation is the
comprehensive 'ti global things we're
trying to affect and the attention to
system events and energies one of the
things we'll committed to as the company
is providing not only well formulated
but really well sourced and well
manufactured product that has not only
levels of purity assured that are you
know we GMP and other regulatory
standards but far exceed those centers
across
and so uh as a veteran
[Music]